<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<event>
 <trivia>
 <question>What current branch of the U.S. military was a corps of only 50 soldiers when World War I broke out</question>
 <answer>The U.S. Air Force</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>What game was created by French mathematician Blaise Pascal, which he discovered when doing experiments into perpetual motion?</question>
 <answer>The Game of Roulette</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>Who said: &quot; I'm the president of the United States and I'm not going to eat any more broccoli &quot;?</question>
 <answer>George Bush</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>What future Soviet dictator was training to be a priest when he got turned on to Marxism?</question>
 <answer>Joseph Stalin</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>What election year saw bumper stickers reading &quot;Wallace, Wallace, Uber Alles&quot;</question>
 <answer>1968</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>Which is the last NPC you have to talk to, to obtain a Portal Stone?</question>
 <answer>Theodoric</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>What color Soul Crystal do you need to have for Acumen SA on Arcana mace?</question>
 <answer>Red</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>How many rooms do the 4 Sepulchers have in total?</question>
 <answer>4</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>When does the Merchant of Mammon appear in Catacombs?</question>
 <answer>Never</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>How many A-grade grandboss jewels exists?</question>
 <answer>3</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>What is the name of the only B-grade grandboss jewel?</question>
 <answer>Ring of queen ant</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>How many Olympiad points does a Noblesse character have at the end of each month, if he does not compete?</question>
 <answer>18</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>When creating a character, you can choose to be a mage or fighter. There is one race that doesn't offer this choice. Which race is that?</question>
 <answer>Dwarf</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>What TV show lost Jim Carrey when he stepped into the movies?</question>
 <answer>In Living Color</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>At which level can you make the Hatchling quest?</question>
 <answer>35</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>What's the name of the item you need to get your clan to level 4?</question>
 <answer>Alliance Manifesto</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>What level does your clan have to be in order to start an Alliance?</question>
 <answer>5</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>Baium is the father of...</question>
 <answer>Frintezza</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>What are the names of the two &quot;teams&quot; on the Seven Signs Quest?</question>
 <answer>Dawn and Dusk</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>How many servers are there on the offical lineage II?</question>
 <answer>8</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>as a fighter, what is the first level when you can learn your first skills?</question>
 <answer>5</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>In what level can you create a clan?</question>
 <answer>10</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>What so-called &quot;war&quot; spawned the dueling slogans &quot;Better Dead Than RED&quot; and &quot;Better Red Than Dead&quot; in the 1950's?</question>
 <answer>The Cold War</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>What president was shot while walking to California Governor Jerry Brown' office?</question>
 <answer>Gerald Ford</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>What modern vehicle was invented to circumvent trench warfare?</question>
 <answer>Tank</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>What congressional award was Dr. Mary Edwards Walker the first woman to receive?</question>
 <answer>Medal of Honor</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>What congressional award was Dr. Mary Edwards Walker the first woman to receive?</question>
 <answer>Medal of Honor</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>In which television series did Roger Moore star from 1962 to 1970?</question>
 <answer>The Saint</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>Who introduced the Betamax video cassette system?</question>
 <answer>Sony</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>What is Bugs Bunny's catchphrase?</question>
 <answer>Eh, whats up Doc?</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>Which Hollywood film maker produced a string of films in the 1950s and 1960s using animals as actors in a drama?</question>
 <answer>Walt Disney</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>Which character made his debut in the silent film Plane Crazy in 1928?</question>
 <answer>Mickey Mouse</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>How did James Dean die?</question>
 <answer>In a car accident</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>Which world-famous cartoon cat was created in 1920 by Pat Sullivan?</question>
 <answer>Felix the Cat</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>Which group flew into the Hotel California?</question>
 <answer>The Eagles</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>Which all time great band featured Harrison and Starkey?</question>
 <answer>The Beatles</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>Arnold Schwarzenegger married the niece of which US president?</question>
 <answer>John F. Kennedy</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>In which city did Steve McQueen take part in the car chase in Bullitt?</question>
 <answer>San Francisco</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>In which movie did Alex Guinness first appear as Ben Obi Wan Kenobi?</question>
 <answer>Star Wars</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>Marlon and Tito were two members of which famous family group?</question>
 <answer>Jackson Five</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>Where did Crazy For You lose half a million dollars before finding success on Broadway?</question>
 <answer>Washington</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>Leslie Rogge was the first person to be arrested due to what?</question>
 <answer>The Internet</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>In 1908 Wilbur Wright traveled what record-breaking number of miles in 2 hours 20 minutes?</question>
 <answer>77</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>How long did Bleriot's first flight across the English Channel last?</question>
 <answer>43 minutes</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>What nationality of plane first broke the 100mph sound barrier?</question>
 <answer>French</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>The first air collision took place over which country?</question>
 <answer>Austria</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>How long did the record-breaking space walk from space shuttle Endeavor last in 1993?</question>
 <answer>Five hours</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>Where did the European space probe Ulysses set off for in 1991?</question>
 <answer>The Sun</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>What was the name of the first probe to send back pictures from Mars?</question>
 <answer>Viking</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>Who was the second Soviet cosmonaut?</question>
 <answer>Titov</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>Who said, &quot;All I need to make a comedy is a park, a policeman and a pretty girl?&quot;</question>
 <answer>Charlie Chaplin</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>In which country did Steve McQueen die?</question>
 <answer>Mexico</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>In 1998 who did Vanity Fair describe as &quot;simply the world's biggest heart throb?&quot;</question>
 <answer>Leonardo DiCaprio</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>In 1998 who did Vanity Fair describe as &quot;simply the world's biggest heart throb?&quot;</question>
 <answer>Leonardo DiCaprio</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>How many friends are there in Friends?</question>
 <answer>Six</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>In which magazine did The Addams Family first appear?</question>
 <answer>New Yorker</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>What is Alpha World?</question>
 <answer>Multi user game</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>What is a MUD?</question>
 <answer>Multi User Computer Game</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>In which European country is the theme park De Efteling?</question>
 <answer>The Netherlands</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>Which ethnic group popularized salsa dancing in New York in the 1980s?</question>
 <answer>Puerto Ricans</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>Which Russian city was famous for its State Circus?</question>
 <answer>Moscow</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>Pokemon is an abbreviation of what?</question>
 <answer>Pocket Monster</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>Who is the Princess in the Super Mario Gang?</question>
 <answer>Daisy</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>What is russian's favourite gambling game?</question>
 <answer>Russian Roulette</answer>
 </trivia>


 <trivia>
 <question>What is russian's favourite drink?</question>
 <answer>Vodka</answer>
 </trivia>

 <trivia>
 <question>What is the quest item used to make a level 5 clan</question>
 <answer>Seal of aspiration</answer>
 </trivia>

</event>